So, after all, let's say that I have finished editing
and I wanna just export my work, you know?
And how I do that by coming,
I know how I do that is by coming on this download button.
And if I click it, as you see, we can specify a file name.
So this is the preview of what we will get.
And we can specify a file name,
as well as a format, either JPG or PNG.
And we also can specify quality.
And then we can either save it to cloud
or by clicking on download,
we'll be able to download it as an image file, you know?
So by clicking on that, let me do that, actually.
Your work is being generated and downloaded.
Yes, as you see, it's downloaded over here.
If I click on open over here, you'll see that
it will be visible in my very device.
So, yep, this is what we got, you see?
And yes, beautiful, actually, beautiful generation.
So yes, what else do we have?
We can view it or we can continue editing this pop-up.
So this was all that we had for the photo editor.